one of the greatest advantages that
最大的优势之一是
comes with using inkscape is having the
使用Inkscape带来的是拥有
ability to create repeat patterns from
能够从创建重复图案
simple shapes objects and even groups of
简单的形状对象，甚至成组的
objects in fact not only can you use
对象实际上不仅可以使用
vector objects to create patterns in
要在其中创建图案的矢量对象
inkscape you can even use text objects
Inkscape您甚至可以使用文本对象
clipped objects and even jpeg images in
中剪切的对象，甚至jpeg图像
this tutorial we'll be showing you
本教程我们将向您展示
exactly how
到底是怎么回事
so getting us started here inkscape
让我们从Inkscape开始
makes the process of turning an object
使旋转物体的过程
into a pattern incredibly easy let me
变成一种难以置信的简单的模式让我
show you what i mean using a simple
向您展示我的意思，使用简单的
shape just to get us started and then
只是为了让我们开始，然后
i'll show you a working example of how
我将向您展示一个工作示例，说明如何
you can actually use this in a practical
你实际上可以把它用在一个实际的
sense
感官
so i'm going to start off with a star
所以我要从一颗星星开始
i'm going to use the stars and polygons
我要用星星和多边形
tool i'm going to choose star instead of
工具，我将选择STAR，而不是
polygon and i'm going to use these input
Polygon和我将使用这些输入
settings right here in case you'd like
设置在这里，以防您想要
to follow along with what i'm doing
去跟随我正在做的事情
now i'm just going to click and drag on
现在我只需点击并拖动
the canvas to create my star i'm going
创造我的明星的画布我要走了
to move the cursor up like that and i'm
把光标像那样向上移动，我就会
going to hold ctrl and ctrl and shift so
按住Ctrl键和Ctrl键并按Shift键
that we have a nice upright star like
我们有一颗很好的竖直的星星
that
那
have a different color grab the
有不同的颜色，抓住
selection tool and let me scale this
选择工具，让我来缩放它
down a little bit i'm going to hold ctrl
稍微往下一点，我要按住Ctrl键
to lock the proportions and scale that
锁定比例并进行缩放
down like that
就这样倒下了
and now to turn this object into a
现在要把这个对象变成一个
pattern all you have to do is make sure
你所要做的就是确保
you have it selected and go to object
您已将其选中并转到对象
pattern and select object to pattern
阵列并选择要阵列的对象
okay now nothing visibly changes on your
好的，现在没有什么明显的变化
canvas but that object will now be
画布，但该对象现在将是
registered as a pattern in your fill and
注册为填充中的图案，并
stroke menu so let me show you how you
笔划菜单，让我向您展示如何
can apply it now i'm going to grab the
可以使用它了，现在我要去拿
rectangle tool i'm going to click and
矩形工具，我要点击并
drag on the canvas to create a simple
拖到画布上可创建简单的
rectangle like that
像这样的长方形
just for the sake of simplicity i'm
只是为了简单起见，我
going to convert this to a path so i'll
我要将它转换为路径，所以我将
go to path and select object to path
转到路径并选择要路径的对象
and now i want to change the fill
现在我想换一下填充物
property of this rectangle from a solid
实体的此矩形的属性
color to a pattern so to do that we're
将颜色添加到图案中，因此我们将
going to use the fill and stroke menu
将使用填充和描边菜单
which is located over here
它位于这里
and what we are looking for is under the
我们要找的东西就在
fill tab we have all of these different
填充选项卡我们有所有这些不同的
options for filling our object we're
填充我们的对象的选项我们正在
looking for this option right here that
在这里寻找这个选项
says pattern when you hover your cursor
当您将光标悬停时会显示图案
over it i'm going to click on that
在它上面，我要点击它
and if you use this drop down right here
如果你使用这里的下拉列表
you should see a list of all the
您应该会看到所有
different patterns that inkscape has in
Inkscape拥有不同的图案
it already now the patterns that you
它现在已经是你的模式了
create custom made patterns are going to
创造定制的图案将会
be labeled as pattern with a series of
被贴上一系列图案的标签
random numbers after it i don't know why
之后的随机数字，我不知道为什么
this is the case uh but for whatever
情况就是这样，呃，但无论如何
reason inkscape will name your patterns
Inkscape会给你的图案命名的原因
this and as far as i know there is no
据我所知，这件事没有
way to change the name of these patterns
更改这些模式名称的方法
so look for something titled pattern
所以去找一些叫花纹的东西吧
3786 or whatever your numbers will be
3786或不管你的数字是多少
and select that
并选择该选项
and uh the the pattern is actually
而且，呃，模式实际上是
applied there you can't really see it
应用在那里，你不能真正看到它
though because it needs to be scaled
不过，因为它需要扩展
down so to scale this down let's work on
为了缩小规模，让我们继续努力
editing our pattern
编辑我们的图案
i'm going to grab the edit pads by nodes
我将按节点获取编辑板
tool over here
工具在这里
and what we are looking for is we're
我们要找的是我们
looking for these handles the first
寻找这些手柄的第一个
handle we're looking for is right here
我们要找的把手就在这里
this little let me zoom in on this this
这一点让我放大这一点
little crosshair this x represents the
小十字线，这个x代表
location of the pattern relative to your
图案相对于您的
object
对象
now if i want to move the location of
现在，如果我想要移动
the pattern i could just click and drag
我只需点击并拖动的图案
this x like this to move the pattern
这个x像这样移动图案
within the object like that you probably
在这样的对象中，您可能
couldn't see exactly what happened there
我看不到那里到底发生了什么
because the pattern's too large i have
因为纸样太大了，我有
to scale it down so let's do that let me
为了缩小规模，让我们这样做吧，让我
zoom out a little bit i'm going to hold
稍微缩小一点，我要保持住
ctrl and roll down the mouse wheel a
按住Ctrl键并向下滚动鼠标滚轮a
couple of times
有几次
and i'm looking for some more handles
我在找更多的把手
out here i don't know why but for some
在这里我不知道为什么，但对一些人来说
reason inkscape puts these handles all
Inkscape将这些句柄全部放置的原因
the way out here in space sometimes so
在太空中的出路有时是这样的
you'll have to look around for them and
你得四处看看，然后
they're tiny too they're hard to see so
它们太小了，很难看得见
we're looking for this square handle
我们在找这个正方形的把手
right here which represents the size of
就在这里，它代表了
the pattern
这种模式
and then we're looking for this circular
然后我们在寻找这份通告
handle right here which represents the
句柄，它表示
rotation of the pattern
图案的旋转
so let me take the square handle over
所以让我来拿这个正方形的把手
here and scale this pattern down i'm
在这里，缩小这个模式，我是
going to hold ctrl
要按住Ctrl键
while i'm doing this i'm bringing the
当我这样做的时候，我会带着
square handle towards the center point
朝向中心点的方形手柄
that crosshair that x and as i do this
当我这样做的时候，它瞄准了那个x
i'm holding ctrl to lock the aspect
我按住Ctrl键锁定方位
ratio and as you can see the pattern is
比例，正如您所看到的，模式是
getting smaller and we're seeing more of
变得越来越小，我们看到更多的
those stars in there let me zoom in on
那里的星星让我把镜头放大
this so you can see this better
这样你就能看得更清楚了
this scaling handle
此缩放句柄
allows you to
使您能够
resize your pattern as needed as you can
尽可能地根据需要调整图案大小
see here and if you want to rotate your
请看这里，如果您想要旋转您的
pattern you can use this handle right
你可以正确地使用这个句柄
here
这里
holding control will lock the rotation
按住Ctrl将锁定旋转
onto 15 degree angles the same as it
在15度角上和它一样
would with any other transformation that
如果有任何其他变化，
you would make in inkscape and again if
你会在Inkscape中制作，如果
you want to move the location of the
您希望将
pattern you just have to click and drag
您只需点击并拖动图案
this crosshair like that and move this
像这样的十字准线，然后移动这个
around as you can see here
就像你在这里看到的那样
and there you go that is how you could
就这样，这就是你可以
take an object and turn it into a simple
把一个物体变成一个简单的
pattern
图案
so let's go over a working example of
因此，让我们来看一个有效的例子
how you would actually use this feature
您将如何实际使用此功能
to create a pattern design
创建图案设计的步骤
for an example here i have this simple
举个例子，我有一个简单的例子
avocado graphic that i created i'm just
我创作的牛油果图片，我只是
going to click and drag over everything
要在所有内容上单击并拖动
here and group all of these shapes
在这里将所有这些形状组合在一起
together by going to object
一起去反对
and selecting
和选择
group now the good thing about working
Group Now工作的好处
with patterns in inkscape is that it
Inkscape中的图案就是它
allows you to create patterns from
允许您从以下位置创建图案
virtually anything it doesn't just have
几乎所有它没有的东西
to be a single shape or a single object
成为单一形状或单一物体
it could be a grouping of objects it
它可以是它的一组对象
could be a text object it could be a
可以是文本对象，也可以是
masked or a clipped object it could even
蒙面或剪裁的物体，它甚至可以
be a jpeg image so virtually anything
是一个jpeg格式的图像，所以几乎任何东西
you want in inkscape can be turned into
你想要的Inkscape可以变成
a pattern okay so i'm going to turn this
一种模式好的，所以我要把这个
group of vector objects into a pattern
将一组矢量对象组合成一个图案
now when i create my pattern i don't
现在，当我创建我的图案时，我不会
want all of the copies of this graphic
我想要此图形的所有副本
to be touching each other side by side
肩并肩地触摸着彼此
as you can see here by the bounding box
正如您在这里的边界框中看到的
what i want to do is increase the size
我想做的是增加尺寸
of that bounding box so that these
这个包围盒，所以这些
objects have some spacing between them
物体之间有一定的间距
as they repeat in the pattern so what
当他们在模式中重复时，那又如何？
i'm going to do is i'm going to copy
我要做的是我要复制
this object i'm going to right click it
我要用鼠标右键单击的对象
and go to copy
然后转到Copy
and i'm going to create a rectangle
我要创建一个矩形
like that
就像这样
and i want to make this rectangle the
我想让这个长方形成为
same size as my object i'm going to go
和我的对象一样大，我要去
to edit
编辑
paste size and i'm going to choose paste
粘贴大小，我将选择粘贴
size
大小
grab the selection tool lower this
抓住选择工具，把这个放下来
beneath the object click and drag over
在对象下方单击并拖动
both of these so we have them both
这两个都有，所以我们都有
selected and i'm going to center this up
被选中，我将把这个放在中心
on the vertical and horizontal axis
在纵轴和横轴上
using the alignment menu which is
使用对齐菜单，该菜单是
located over here
位于这里
it should open up on the right hand side
它应该在右手边打开
of your screen and i want last selected
我想要最后一次选择
chosen from this drop down and i'm just
从这个下拉列表中选择，我只是
going to align this on the vertical and
将这个垂直对齐，
horizontal axis like that
像这样的水平轴
okay so now i'm going to click off of
好的，现在我要点击
this to deselect everything what i want
这是为了取消选择我想要的一切
to do now is take this object and add
现在要做的就是获取该对象并添加
some padding around it so that we have
它周围有一些垫子，这样我们就有了
some spacing going around this avocado
这个鳄梨周围有一些间隔
graphic
图解
so what i'm going to do up here where it
所以我要在这里做的是
says the width 328 i'm just going to add
上面写着宽度328，我要加上
100 to each dimension so i'm going to
每个维度100，所以我要
make this
把这个做好
uh 400
呃400
and i'm going to make this over here the
我要把这件事变成
height
高度
and now we have a little bit of padding
现在我们有了一点填充物
there let me center that up center that
好了，让我把那个放在中间
up let me see how that looks okay we
让我看看它看起来怎么样我们
have some more pattern but maybe not as
有更多的模式，但可能不像
much as i'd like i'm going to add
尽管我很乐意，但我还是要补充一点
another 100 to each dimension so let me
每个维度再加100，所以让我
make this 500
加到500块吧
and then i'll make this one 600
然后我会把这个做成600
and let me try that again let me center
让我再试一次，让我居中
that up
那就好了
okay that looks a little better
好的，看起来好一点了。
so now i'm going to grop i'm going to
所以现在我要摸索我要去
group these two objects together i'll go
把这两件东西组合在一起，我去
to object and select
要反对并选择
group
群组
and i'm just going to scale this down
我只想把这件事缩小
and put this off to the side
把这个放在一边
i'm going to select this make sure i
我要选择这个来确保我
have it selected go to object
将其选中转到对象
pattern
图案
objects to pattern and let's say i want
对象的模式，假设我想要
to use this as a background for like a
以此作为背景，就像是
thumbnail i'm going to design the
我要设计的缩略图是
average thumbnail design is 1280 by 720
平均缩略图设计为1280x720
pixels so i'm going to grab the
像素，所以我要抓取
rectangle tool
矩形工具
click and drag like that and let me grab
像这样点击并拖动，让我抓起
my selection tool and i'm going to
我的选择工具和我要去
change the width and height of this to
将此对象的宽度和高度更改为
by 720 like that and i want to resize my
像这样的720，我想调整我的
canvas to fit this object so i'm going
画布来适应这个物体，所以我要
to select the object and press ctrl
选择对象并按Ctrl键
shift and r on the keyboard and it'll
按住键盘上的Shift和r键，它将
resize the document to fit that object
调整文档大小以适合该对象
now i'm going to take this object right
现在我要把这个物体看得很清楚
here
这里
go back to the fill and stroke menu and
返回到填充和描边菜单，然后
i'm going to choose my pattern and as
我要选择我的图案，因为
you can see there's the pattern so what
你可以看到模式，那又如何？
i want to do is grab the edit paths by
我想做的是通过以下方式抓取编辑路径
nodes tool
节点工具
and look for the placement put that in
找出把它放进去的位置
the center
中心
look for the scaling handle scale that
寻找缩放手柄的比例
down
降下来
oops
哎呀
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and as you can see we have our avocado
如你所见，我们有鳄梨
pattern that we created
我们创建的模式
using inkscape and i could even rotate
使用Inkscape和我甚至可以旋转
this around a little bit just to give it
这一点只是为了给它
a little bit of a
有点像是
design flare there we go
设计火炬，我们来了
okay you got to make sure you're
好的，你得确保你是
grabbing the correct cross hair here
在这里抓住正确的十字交叉
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and there we go that is how you could
我们走吧，这就是你如何
take a simple object and turn it into a
拿一个简单的物体，把它变成一个
repeat pattern that you can use to fill
重复您可以用来填充的图案
objects however you'd like in inkscape
水墨景观中您喜欢的对象
before i end this video if you found
如果您发现，在我结束此视频之前
this lesson useful then consider
这堂课很有用，然后考虑一下
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的水墨风景大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
它包含60多个视频
where i go over all of the tools and
我检查了所有的工具，
features in inkscape and i explain what
水墨景观中的特征，我解释了什么
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示它们如何工作
kind of like how i did in this video we
有点像我在这个视频中所做的那样，
even have a private community where you
甚至有一个私人社区，您
can ask questions and get help from me
可以向我提出问题并寻求帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何时候您想要的，最重要的是，有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
只需支付每月会员费
17 one time and you're in for life i'll
17一次，你就会终身监禁，我会
have some information about that in the
有一些相关信息
description of the video if you want to
如果您想的话，可以描述视频
check that out as always thanks for
一如既往地检查一下谢谢
watching
看
you
你